I'm Peppa Pig.
[OINKS]
This is my little brother
George.
This is mummy Pig.
And this is daddy Pig.
[OINKS]
[LAUGHTER]
Peppa Pig. Oink.
[PEPPA READS
ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Mummy and Daddy Pig
have just made breakfast
for Peppa and George.
Oink! Breakfast is ready!
[GEORGE OINKS,
THEN LAUGHS]
Oink!
Peppa has red spots
on her face!
Mummy, I don't feel
very well. Oink!
Oh dear, Peppa.
You don't look very well.
Oink! Don't worry.
I'll ring Doctor Brown-Bear.
Doctor Brown-Bear speaking.
Oink!
Peppa is not very well.
Her face is covered
in red spots!
Hmm. Put Peppa to bed
and I'll come straight round.
Doctor Brown-Bear
has come to make Peppa better.
Hello Peppa,
how are you today?
I am not very well.
Stick your tongue out,
please.
Hmm. It's not
anything serious.
Peppa has just got a rash.
Oink!
Do I need medicine?
The rash will
clear up quickly.
But if you like, I can give
you just a little medicine.
Yes, please.
I'm afraid it doesn't
taste very nice.
Open wide please.
Yuck! Disgusting!
You are a brave little one
for taking it so well.
Peppa must stay in bed.
I'll call back later
to check that she is better.
Oink!
Can Peppa have visitors?
Oh yes,
she can have visitors.
The rash isn't catching.
Goodbye!
Oink!
Goodbye Doctor Brown-Bear!
Mummy, can I get up now?
Doctor Brown-Bear
says that you must
stay in bed for
a little bit Peppa.
[SIGHING]
But it's so boring!
Doctor Brown-Bear did say
you could have visitors.
Oink!
Can Suzy Sheep visit me?
Suzy Sheep
is Peppa's best friend.
I'll ring Suzy Sheep's mummy.
Bleat!
Hello Mrs. Pig.
Oink! May Peppa talk
with Suzy please?
Oink! Hello, Suzy!
Bleat! Hello, Peppa.
I'm not very well.
I have red spots on my face.
Has the doctor been?
Yes, Doctor Brown-Bear was here!
He said I was not very well
and that I was very brave.
So are you really ill?
Yes, yes!
It's not pretend!
I have to stay in bed! Oink!
Doctor Brown-Bear
gave me medicine
that tasted
really horrible!
I'm coming to see you! Bleat!
I'm going to wear
my nurse's outfit!
Suzy Sheep
has come to see Peppa.
Suzy is wearing
her nurse's costume.
[LAUGHING]
Danny Dog and Rebecca Rabbit
have come along too.
Hello Peppa!
Oink! Hello!
Bleat!
How do you feel?
I am not very well, Suzy.
I have to stay in bed.
What can we do
to make you better?
Oink! You could get
me some orange juice.
Okay!
[LAUGHTER]
Peppa seems to be
quite enjoying herself.
[LAUGHS]
Thank you, Suzy.
Do you feel any better?
A little bit. Oink!
Danny?
Woof!
Ask my mummy if I could
have some ice cream.
And Rebecca, could you bring me
some flowers from the garden?
Doctor Brown-Bear is here,
to see if Peppa is better.
Ah good, the nurse
is already here!
How is the patient?
Um, I'm not a real nurse,
it's just pretend.
I see.
Would you like me to
take a look myself?
Yes, please.
I say!
No more red spots!
You're completely better!
Aren't I still a bit ill?
How do you feel?
I think I should stay
in bed a little bit more.
Hm. Oink!
I fancy a game with
this ball, in the garden!!
Who wants to join me?
Me! Me! Me!
Me, too! Oink! Oink!
[LAUGHTER]
Well I never!
A complete recovery!
[LAUGHTER]
[PEPPA READING
ONSCREEN TEXT]
Peppa and George
are very exited today.
It is snowing outside!
Oink! Mummy! Can we go
and play in the snow?
Oink! Yes.
But it's very cold outside,
so you must
wrap up warm.
Hurrah!
Oink!
[LAUGHING]
And don't forget to wear your
hats, and scarves and gloves.
[LAUGHING]
It is very cold outside.
Peppa and George
must wear their hats,
and scarves,
and gloves.
[LAUGHING]
Oink!
Come on George! Oink!
[LAUGHING]
Peppa and George are making
footprints in the snow.
[OINKS,
THEN LAUGHS]
Peppa and George love making
footprints in the snow!
[LAUGHING]
[YELPS]
Oh, dear.
[LAUGHS]
It's not funny.
[LAUGHS,
THEN OINKS]
[LAUGHING]
Oink!
George, let's play snowballs!
Peppa has made a snowball.
[LAUGHS,
THEN OINKS]
[LAUGHING]
Peppa and George
are having a lot of fun.
George, come back,
you little piggy
[LAUGHING]
Oink! Oink!
Ah! Oink!
[LAUGHING]
Oink!
[WAILING]
Oh, dear. Maybe this game
is getting a little too rough.
Oink!
Sorry, George.
[SOBS]
George!
Let's build a snowman!
Oink!
[LAUGHING]
Peppa and George
are making a snowman.
First they make the body.
Oink! George, this
is the snowman's body.
Now, they make
the snowman's head.
Oink! Now he needs some
arms and eyes and a mouth!
George has found some sticks
for the snowman's arms.
Peppa has found some stones for
the snowman's eyes and mouth.
This is his face.
Oink!
Now the snowman
needs a nose.
Peppa has got a carrot,
to make the snowman's nose.
Oink! Oink!
The snowman looks very happy.
But maybe he is bit cold.
Oink! The snowman needs some
clothes, to keep him warm.
[OINKS,
THEN LAUGHS]
George has found some clothes
to keep the snowman
nice and warm!
[LAUGHS,
THEN OINKS]
[LAUGHING]
The snowman
is wearing his hat,
and scarf,
and gloves.
Mummy! Daddy!
Oink! Come and look!
Oink! Oink!
Mummy is wearing her hat
and scarf and gloves.
Oink! That is the best
snowman I have ever seen!
[SHIVERING]
Daddy Pig looks quite cold.
He isn't wearing
his hat and scarf and gloves.
[SNEEZES,
THEN OINKS]
Daddy, why aren't you wearing
your hat, and scarf and gloves?
I don't know where
they are! Oink!
I can't find them anywhere!
Oink! I think I know where
Daddy's hat,
scarf and gloves are.
Daddy Pig's hat and scarf
and gloves are on the Snowman!
Oh!
[LAUGHING]
[PEPPA READING
ONSCREEN TEXT]
[LAUGHING]
Peppa and her family
are going out for the day.
Oink! Peppa, George.
Today we are going
to Windy Castle!
What's Windy Castle, Daddy?
It's a castle,
on a very high hill!
Oink! Oink!
George likes castles.
Oink! Windy Castle sounds
like a boring thing for boys.
No Peppa, you'll love it.
There's a great view from
the top of Windy Castle.
You can even see
Granny and Grandpa's house!
Wow! Let's go!
[LAUGHING]
I'll map-read
and Mummy Pig will drive.
MUMMY PIG:
Are you sure, Daddy Pig?
When you map-read we always
get lost and you get grumpy.
Oink! We will not get lost
and I will not get grumpy.
[LAUGHING]
Windy Castle, here we come!
[CAR HONKS]
Are we nearly
there yet?
Not quite.
Oh.
Would you like to play a game?
Yes, please. Oink!
Let's play “I Spy!”
Okay.
I'll go first.
Daddy has to secretly
look at something
and the others
guess what it is.
I spy with my little eye,
something colored red.
Red? Oink!
My dress! That's red!
No. It's not
your dress.
Hmm.
The car!
That's right!
Our red car.
[CAR HONKS]
[LAUGHTER]
My go.
I spy with my little eye,
something blue.
DADDY PIG:
Hm, George's blue shirt!
Nope.
Is it something in the car?
No. Give up?
Yes.
The sky! The blue sky! Oink!
I win.
[LAUGHTER]
Daddy Pig?
Do you know where we are?
I know exactly where we are.
Although...
This road doesn't look
the same as it does on the map.
Oh, Daddy Pig! Oink!
We're lost!
We are not lost.
So how do we get
to Windy Castle from here?
Just give me a moment.
Hm!
I know, we can
ring Granny and Grandpa.
There's no need to ring
Granny and Grandpa. Oink!
I'll get us to Windy Castle,
if it takes me all day.
We haven't got all day.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello.
Grandpa Pig speaking.
Grandpa Pig, we've got a bit
lost on the way to Windy Castle.
[LAUGHS]
Is Daddy Pig doing
the map-reading?
[LAUGHING]
Yes, Daddy Pig
is doing the map-reading.
And he's a bit grumpy
at the moment.
I am not grumpy. Oink!
[LAUGHS]
Oink!
This is the best route:
keep on the main road until
you see Windy Castle up ahead.
Thank you Grandpa Pig.
We follow the main road
and look out for Windy Castle.
As I thought.
[LAUGHTER]
Look!
Is that a castle?
DADDY PIG:
Yes! It's Windy Castle!
[ENGINE STRAINING]
Come on car!
You can make it!
Hurray!
Peppa and her family have
arrived at Windy Castle.
Wow!
It's so tall!
Oink! Oink!
Let's go inside.
The view from the top
is fantastic!
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
CHILDREN:
Wow!
MUMMY PIG:
Look at the view!
PEPPA:
Mummy, is that
Granny and Grandpa's house?
MUMMY PIG:
Yes, it is!
PEPPA:
It's so far away!
Let's take a look
through the telescope.
Can I look
first, please?
Yes, but you must
let George look next.
Wow!
The telescope makes
everything look bigger.
PEPPA:
I can see Granny and Grandpa!
Look George!
Oink!
GEORGE:
Gangy 'ig!
Baba 'ig!
George is waving
at Granny and Grandpa Pig.
Silly George! Oink!
Granny and Grandpa are too
far away to see you waving!
I know!
We can ring them!
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
MUMMY PIG:
Grandpa Pig! We can see you
from Windy Castle!
Wave at us!
GEORGE:
Granny and Grandpa
are waving at us!
[LAUGHING]
I love Windy Castle!
[PEPPA READING
ONSCREEN TEXT]
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
Peppa and George
are playing in the garden.
Too me, George.
You threw the ball
too hard George!
So the rules say
I win! Oink!
Now it's my turn.
[LAUGHS,
THEN OINKS]
I win again!
Oink!
Peppa, George.
Today your big cousin,
Chloé is coming to visit!
Yippee! Cousin Chloé!
Oink! Oink!
George, Chloé
is a big girl, like me.
So, don't be sad if she finds
you too little to play with.
I'm sure Chloé will
play with both of you.
[CAR HONKS]
Chloé's here! Oink!
Aunty Pig has brought Chloé
to spend the day
at Peppa's house.
Chloé is Peppa and George's
cousin.
Chloé is a bit older
than Peppa and George.
Oink! Hello Chloé!
Oink! Oink!
Hello Peppa! Hello George!
Oink!
[LAUGHING]
See you later!
Do you want to play a game?
Oink! Yes!
Let's play "Catch!"
Peppa loves playing "Catch".
Do you still
play "Catch"?
That's a game
for little children.
Oh. We only play "Catch"
because George likes it.
Okay. Let's play
it for George.
Do you play with proper rules
or the baby rules?
Proper rules!
I'll start. Oink!
Peppa, you're "it".
Catch me if you can!
Oink!
Peppa is "it".
She has to chase
Chloé and George.
[LAUGHING]
Can't catch me!
George!
I'm going to easily catch you!
You're so little!
[LAUGHING]
Oink! That's not fair!
You're helping George!
That's because he's little.
Oink!
Do you want me to help you?
No! I don't need help.
I'm a big girl like you.
Come on then, Peppa!
Try and catch us!
[LAUGHING]
Can't catch us!
[PANTING]
This is a silly game.
Can we play something else?
Okay, I know a really good game,
for big children.
It's called "Sly Fox"!
Oink!
"Sly Fox"?
I want to play "Sly Fox"!
What is it?
One person is the “Sly Fox”.
Oink!
And the others
creep up on them.
Oink! Me! Me!
I want to be the “Sly Fox”!
Peppa is the "Sly Fox".
While her back is turned,
the others creep up on her.
But if Peppa turns
and sees someone move,
they have to go
back to the start!
George! I saw you move!
Back to the start!
[LAUGHS]
Got you! I win!
You moved before
I was ready!
The rules say
I can move when I like.
Don't they George?
Oink! Oink!
Now it's Chloé's
turn to be the sly fox.
Peppa and George
must stay very still.
[YELPS]
Peppa!
I saw you move!
Back to the start!
Oink! It's not fair!
You looked too long!
The rules say,
I can look as long as I want.
Oink! Back to the start.
[LAUGHS,
THEN OINKS]
George is the winner!
[LAUGHING]
Can we play
a different game?
Yes. Oink! But as long
as it's a grown-up game.
I know! Oink!
Let's play my favorite game!
It's very grown-up!
George, do you know what
Peppa's favorite game is?
Oink! Oink!
Peppa's favorite game
is jumping up and down
in muddy puddles!
George, if you jump in puddles,
you must wear your boots!
Oink!
I've brought some boots
for you too, Chloé!
I'm too grown-up to
jump in muddy puddles.
Oh. So am I.
[LAUGHING]
George loves
jumping in muddy puddles
Secretly, Peppa would
love to jump in the puddle.
But she wants
to look grown-up.
I hear there's some
puddle jumping going on!
Mummy and Daddy Pig
love jumping in muddy puddles!
It does look fun.
Yes, it does.
[LAUGHING]
Maybe there's
a rule that says,
big girls can jump
in muddy puddles.
Yes!
That's a good rule! Oink!
Race you!
Peppa and Chloé love
jumping in muddy puddles!
Everyone loves jumping
up and down in muddy puddles,
even grown-up girls!
[LAUGHING]
[♪♪♪]
[GIGGLING]
PEPPA:
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING, GIGGLING]
[GRUNTING]